<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fspxnky</title><link>https://fspxnky.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on fspxnky</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 19:32:35 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fspxnky.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Legacy (Easy-Windows Machine)</title><link>https://fspxnky.github.io/legacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 19:32:35 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fspxnky.github.io/legacy/</guid><description>This machine in HackTheBox is rated Easy. It encourage me to do a vuln scan on the open port. Personally I feel scanning is important for this box because if you miss a certain scan, you will miss out the vulnerability. I was stuck for a few hours because I dont know where to look for after the attempt to list the shared directory fail.
Machine IP: 10.10.10.4; Machine Author: ch4p</description></item><item><title>Fall</title><link>https://fspxnky.github.io/fall/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 19:05:23 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fspxnky.github.io/fall/</guid><description>To celebrate the fifth year that the author has survived his infosec career, a new box has been born! This machine resembles a few different machines in the PEN-200 environment (making it yet another OSCP-like box). More enumeration practice indeed!
Feel free to contact the author at https://donavan.sg/blog if you would like to drop a comment.
The machine IP address is 192.168.50.113 for me, yours will be different. Do scan your network before proceeding with the attack.</description></item><item><title>Joy</title><link>https://fspxnky.github.io/joy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 10:18:12 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fspxnky.github.io/joy/</guid><description>Does penetration testing spark joy? If it does, this machine is for you.
This machine is full of services, full of fun, but how many ways are there to align the stars? Perhaps, just like the child in all of us, we may find joy in a playground such as this.
This is somewhat OSCP-like for learning value, but is nowhere as easy to complete with an OSCP exam timeframe. But if you found this box because of preparation for the OSCP, you might as well try harder.</description></item><item><title>Mercy</title><link>https://fspxnky.github.io/mercy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 16:11:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fspxnky.github.io/mercy/</guid><description>MERCY is a machine dedicated to Offensive Security for the PWK course. MERCY is a name-play on some aspects of the PWK course. It is NOT a hint for the box.
MERCY is a VirtualBox VM built, but I host it on Proxmox Server. To get the VM image, click here.
Feel free to contact the author at https://donavan.sg/blog if you would like to drop a comment.
The machine IP address is 192.</description></item><item><title>Development</title><link>https://fspxnky.github.io/development/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 02:50:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fspxnky.github.io/development/</guid><description>This machine reminds us of a DEVELOPMENT environment: misconfigurations rule the roost. This is designed for OSCP practice, and the original version of the machine was used for a CTF. It is now revived, and made more nefarious than the original. Development is a VirtualBox VM built, but I host it on Proxmox Server. To get the VM image, click here.
Feel free to contact the author at https://donavan.sg/blog if you would like to drop a comment.</description></item><item><title>Bravery</title><link>https://fspxnky.github.io/bravery/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 17:46:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fspxnky.github.io/bravery/</guid><description>This machine hopes to inspire BRAVERY in you; this machine may surprise you from the outside. This is designed for OSCP practise, and the original version of the machine was used for a CTF. It is now revived, and made more nefarious than the original. BRAVERY is a VirtualBox VM built, but I host it on Proxmox Server. To get the VM image, click here.
Feel free to contact the author at https://donavan.</description></item><item><title>DC-9</title><link>https://fspxnky.github.io/dc-9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 17:46:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fspxnky.github.io/dc-9/</guid><description>DC-9 is another purposely built vulnerable lab to gain experience in the world of penetration testing. The ultimate goal of this challenge is to get root and to read the only flag. DC-9 is a VirtualBox VM built, but I host it on Proxmox Server. To get the VM image, click here.
Thanks to @DCAU7 and the team for creating this machine.
The machine IP address is 192.168.50.108 for me, yours will be different.</description></item><item><title>Setting up Vuln Lab in Proxmox</title><link>https://fspxnky.github.io/settingupvulnlab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 22:11:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fspxnky.github.io/settingupvulnlab/</guid><description>The machine i downloaded and install are from NetSecFocus Trophy Room, under the vulnhub section. I will install the machine highligted in the red section into my proxmox.
I only manage to install 32 machines out of 38 into the proxmox.
6 Machines that i didn&amp;rsquo;t installed due to:
Healthcare - (Too old for it to work, maybe?) Photography - (File too big for unknown reason : 500GB) GlasgowSmile - (Cannot boot, lead to grub rescue) Breach 3 - (Got IP in Proxmox but appear offline) LordoftheRoot - (Got IP in Proxmox but appear offline) Alpha 1 - (Link Broken) Download Vulnerable Machine from Vulnhub First, lets download 1 machine from vulnhub.</description></item></channel></rss>